Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Collection of Annotated Scores, 1828-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Oversized, 1960-1989, III.; Folder 877-Folder 903
  - Casavant, Charles Just as I am: from the diary of Nijinsky, 1976, 1 score (49 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For piano, tape of pre-recorded pianos, narrator, gong, and electronics Contains some performance markings. (Box 36, Folder 0882)
  - Cohen, Douglas, 1959- G, 1987, 1 score (7 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings, including duration, tempo, and fingerings. (Box 36, Folder 0883)
  - Cohen, Douglas, 1959- Three songs on texts by Albert Giraud, 1989, 1 score (12 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For soprano, violin, and piano Contains performance markings, including fingerings and durations. Additional name: Giraud, Albert, 1860-1929 (Box 36, Folder 0884)
    Landschaft -- A mon cousin de Bergame -- Die Harfe.
  - Dittrich, Paul-Heinz Concert avec plusieurs instruments no. IV pour piano et orchestra (Ursonate), undated, 1 score (54 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For piano and orchestra Pages 44-54 are on two sheets, top and bottom, for each page of score. (Box 36, Folder 0885)
  - Eakin, Charles, 1927- Being of sound mind, undated, 1 score (56 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For speakers and chamber ensemble Contains performance markings. Based on a play by Gene McKinney. Additional name: McKinney, Eugene, 1922- (Box 36, Folder 0886)
  - Fennimore, Joseph Bits and Pieces: piano suite, 1970, 1 score(9 pages); Print Marks Music Instrumentation: For solo piano Inscribed to Mikhashoff, by composer. Not oversized. (Box 36, Folder 0887)
  - Hachimura, Yoshio, 1938-1985 Constellation op. 5, 1969, 1 score (20 pages); Manuscript (ozalid copy) Instrumentation: For violin, vibraphone, tubular bells, and piano Contains performance markings. Alternative title: Seishin-fu. (Box 36, Folder 0888)
  - Hiller, Lejaren, 1924-1994 Minuet and trio (the music lesson), 1980, 1 score (12 pages); Holograph (Photocopy) Instrumentation: Operatic scene, for narrator, soprano voice, piccolo, violoncello, percussion, and piano. Contains performance markings. Text by Webster Smalley. Not oversized. Additional name: Smalley, Webster (Box 36, Folder 0889)
  - Hovhaness, Alan, 1911-2000 Visionary landscapes, 1967, 1 score (13 pages); Print C. F. Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 36, Folder 0890)
  - Monahan, Gordon Piano mechanics, 1986, 1 score (12 pages); Print (negative blueprints) Instrumentation: For solo piano Includes letter from composer to Mikhashoff. (Box 36, Folder 0891)
    Voices emerging along high-tension wires -- Abrupt stops -- Solitary waves and far away sounds -- Far away sounds -- Trill with hand controlled pitch release -- Solitary waves -- Melody concealed by a tremolo -- High trills becoming combination tones -- Fingers and arms becoming four hands.
  - Nørholm, Ib Fluktuationer: für 39 Saiteninstrumente, op. 25 (1962), 1967, 1 score (47 pages); Print D. Fog Musikforlag Instrumentation: For string orchestra, including 2 harps, harpsichord, mandolin, and guitar Inscribed To Mikhashoff by the composer. (Box 36, Folder 0892)
  - Roxbury, Ronald, 1946-1986 Brou-haha, undated, 1 score (4 leaves); Holograph (ozalid copy) Instrumentation: For two pianos, 7 hands Lacking title page. Work's title confirmed by William Bland. (Box 36, Folder 0893)
  - Speech, Bernadette, 1948- Between the lines, 1984, 1 score (8 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For violin, vibraphone, and piano Violin part marked for performance. (Box 36, Folder 0894)
  - White, John, 1936- Piano sonata no. 96 (The Caledonian), undated, 1 score (2 pages); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings. (Box 36, Folder 0895)
  - Ye, Xiaogang Hsu shih = Ballade: opus 25, undated, 1 score (11 pages); Manuscript (Photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano (Box 36, Folder 0896)
  - Cage, John Concert for piano and orchestra (1957-58), 1960, 1 conductor's score and 14 parts; Print Henmar Press/Peters Instrumentation: For piano and orchestra Parts are marked for performance. Signed by Mikhashoff. The piano part is a photocopy larger than the container for the other parts. (Box 37, Folder 0897)
    Parts for piano, violin 1-3, viola 1-2, cello, bass, flute, bassoon, trumpet, trombone, and tuba.
  - Cage, John Theatre piece, 1960, 8 parts (18 leaves each); Print Henmar Press/Peters Instrumentation: Parts are provided for 1 to 8 performers (musicians, dancers, singers, etc.)--to be used in whole or part, in any combination. Signed by Mikhashoff. A transparency is included with each part. Also included: typescript performance instructions (1 leaf) for Performance of June 22, 1977 and handwritten notes (3 leaves) by someone other than Mikhashoff. (Box 37, Folder 0898)
  - Cage, John Music for (title to be completed by adding the number of players performing), 1984, 12 parts; Print Henmar Press Instrumentation: For unspecified combination of voices and instruments Some parts contain partly erased performance markings. Signed by Mikhashoff (Box 38, Folder 0899)
    Parts for: Piano, Violin 1-2, Viola, Cello, Flute, Clarinet, Percussion 1, 2 (2 copies), 3, 4
  - Henze, Hans Werner, 1926-2012 English cat. Vocal score, 1983, 1 score (379 pages); Print Schott Instrumentation: For voices and piano accompaniment Preliminary page marked with ten locations in the score that could be excerpted. (Box 38, Folder 0900)
  - Unknown Unidentified, undated, 1 score (1 page); Print (Graphic Notation) OVERSIZED. Graphic Notation. Includes one copy, not marked. (Box Map drawer, Folder 0901)
  - Zandi, Bahman M., 1944- Processus: pour piano, undated, 1 score (1 page); Manuscript (reproduction) Instrumentation: For solo piano OVERSIZED. Instructions on the back. (Box Map Drawer, Folder 0902)
  - Cage, John 49 waltzes for the five boroughs: waltz no. 1 (Manhattan); waltz no. 2 (Bronx and Richmond); waltz no. 3 (Brooklyn-Queens), undated, 3 scores; Manuscript Instrumentation: For solo piano or two pianos Some alterations are indicated. Three realizations by Yvar Mikhashoff on vellum, inserted between pages 462-463 (Waltz 1) and pages 464-465 (Waltz 2B and Waltz 3). (Box 37, Folder 0903)
- Additional annotated scores, 1903-1982, IV.; Folder 904-Folder 917
  This series contains 13 scores with performance or analytical markings added to the collection after initial processing had been completed.
  - Aronson, Maurice Pianist's digest: 250 excerpts taken from the great masterworks for piano, 1945, 1 score (180 pages); Print Edward B. Marks Music Instrumentation: For solo piano Some markings on page 177. (Box 39, Folder 0904)
  - Boulez, Pierre, 1925- Troisième sonate pour piano. Formant 2: Trope, 1961, 1 score (16 leaves); Print (photocopy) Universal Edition Instrumentation: For solo piano The score has been color coded. (Box 39, Folder 0905)
  - Bussotti, Sylvano Piano piece no. 5 for David Tudor, undated, 1 score (4 pages); Manuscript (ink) Instrumentation: For solo piano. Some deletions made using white-out fluid. This is Mikhashoff's re-notated version. Additional name: Mikhashoff, Yvar, 1941-1993 (Box 39, Folder 0906)
  - Bussotti, Sylvano Pièces de chair, no. 2. Parfum, undated, 2 scores (1 leaf each); Manuscript Instrumentation: Unspecified, but possibly for baritone, piano, and violoncello The photocopy of published score is marked with vertical divisions; the manuscript score contains a few performance indications. Consists of ink manuscript of Yvar Mikhashoff's re-notated version and a photocopy of the same music as published. Additional name: Mikhashoff, Yvar, 1941-1993 (Box 39, Folder 0907)
  - Bussotti, Sylvano Sette fogli. Per tre sul piano and Sensitivo, 1963, 1 score (2 leaves); Manuscript (photocopy) Universal Edition Instrumentation: For solo piano (1st work) Heavily marked for performance. (Box 39, Folder 0908)
  - Cage, John Concerto for prepared piano and chamber orchestra, 1960, 1 part (16 leaves); Manuscript (photocopy) Henmar Press Instrumentation: For prepared piano and chamber orchestra Color coded in preparation for performance. Solo piano part only. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 39, Folder 0909)
  - Finney, Ross Lee, 1906-1997 Variations on a theme by Alban Berg, 1977, 1 score (12 pages); Print Edition Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings, including fingerings. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 39, Folder 0910)
  - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 Sonata h-moll für Klavier zu 2 Händen, 1945, 1 score (35 pages); Print C. F. Peters Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings throughout. Signed Yvar Mikhashoff. (Box 39, Folder 0911)
  - Liszt, Franz, 1811-1886 Twenty original piano compositions, 1903, 1 score (xiii, 147 pages); Print Oliver Ditson Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains small number of performance markings. Additional name: Spanuth, August, 1857-1920 (Box 39, Folder 0912)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750 Art of fugue. Selections, 1982, 3 scores; Holograph (pencil) Instrumentation: For orchestra, string orchestra, and instrumental ensemble Three arrangements by Michael McCandless of two fugues from Bach's Art of fugue. Additional name: McCandless, Michael, 1957-1993 (Box 39, Folder 0913)
    Fuga 1 a 4 voci [BWV 1080/1] arranged for full orchestra -- [Fuga 4: BWV 1080/4] arranged for string orchestra (incomplete) -- Fuga 1 a 4 voci [BWV 1080/1] arranged for instrumental ensemble (incomplete).
  - Palmer, Robert, 1915-2010 Epigrams, no. 1-3, 1960, 1 score (13 pages); Print (photocopy) Peer International Instrumentation: For solo piano Edited by John Kirkpatrick. Inscription on outside leaf: "I have corrected several errors in the published copy!", possibly in the hand of Palmer or Kirkpatrick. Additional name: Kirkpatrick, John, 1905-1991 (Box 39, Folder 0914)
  - Rudhyar, Dane, 1895-1985 Rite of transcendance, undated, 1 score (10 pages); Manuscript (ink) Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains some corrections and performance markings. Annotated and recopied by Yvar Mikhashoff. Signed by Mikhashoff. Additional name: Mikhashoff, Yvar, 1941-1993 (Box 39, Folder 0915)
  - Smit, Leo, 1921-1999 Attacca lo scherzo, undated, 1 score (10 leaves); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Contains performance markings, including additional time signatures. (Box 39, Folder 0916)
  - Smit, Leo, 1921-1999 Variations for piano and small orchestra, 1981, 1 part (30 pages); Manuscript (ink) Instrumentation: Part for solo piano Contains performance markings and additional orchestral cues. Solo piano part as written out by Yvar Mikhashoff. Additional name: Mikhashoff, Yvar, 1941-1993 (Box 39, Folder 0917)
- Additional unmarked scores, 1906-1993, V.; Folder 918-Folder 961
  This series contains 43 unmarked scores added to the collection after initial processing had been completed.
  - Arnold, Martin, 1959- Cathedra (after Barnett Newman), 1985, 1 score (8 leaves); Holograph (ink) Instrumentation: For violin and piano Not marked. (Box 39, Folder 0918)
  - Berkson, [unidentified forename] Movement for piano, 1972, 1 score (10 leaves); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 39, Folder 0919)
  - Borowski, Felix, 1872-1956 Valsette, undated, 1 score (3 leaves); Print (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 39, Folder 0920)
  - Bussotti, Sylvano Bergkristall. Brillante, 1978, 1 score (11 pages); Print Ricordi Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 39, Folder 0921)
  - Bussotti, Sylvano Passion selon Sade. Tableaux vivants, 1977, 2 scores (8 pages each); Print (reproduction of manuscript) Ricordi Instrumentation: For 2 pianos Not marked. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 39, Folder 0922)
  - Bussotti, Sylvano Pieces for David Tudor, undated, 5 transparencies; Manuscript Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. The score of each of the 5 pieces is reproduced on a transparency. (Box 39, Folder 0923)
  - Bussotti, Sylvano Pour clavier, 1962, 1 score (23 pages); Print (reproduced from manuscript) Moeck Verlag Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. Signed by Mikhashoff. (Box 39, Folder 0924)
  - Bussotti, Sylvano Siciliano per dodici voci maschili, 1960, 1 score (3 leaves); Print (reproduction of manuscript) Instrumentation: for choir of 12 male singers Not marked. Printed on 3 transparencies. (Box 39, Folder 0925)
  - Bussotti, Sylvano Ultima rara (pop song) [incomplete], 1976, 1 score (1 page); Print (reproduction of manuscript) Ricordi Instrumentation: For 1-3 instruments or voices with guitar Not marked. Signed by Mikhashoff. Missing pages 2-3. (Box 39, Folder 0926)
  - Chaplin, Alan Low Dutch tune from the Bay Psalm Book set after the style of an early American fuging tune for thirteen instruments, 1970s, 1 score (8 leaves); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For instrumental ensemble Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0927)
  - Chopin, Frédéric, 1810-1849 Mazurka, op. 67 no. 3, 1991, 1 score (4 leaves); Manuscript (pencil) Instrumentation: Originally for solo piano, arranged for violin and piano Not marked. Arranged for violin and piano by Thomas Halpin. Additional name: Halpin, Thomas (Box 40, Folder 0928)
  - Clarke, Symon Ouvrage en mosaïque, 1984, 1 score (38 pages); Manuscript (reproduction) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0929)
  - Cowell, Henry, 1897-1965 Two woofs, 1947, 1 score 12 pages); Print New Music Edition Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. Additional title: 20th anniversary edition piano works by Charles Ives, Henry Cowell, Carl Ruggles. (Box 40, Folder 0930)
    Two woofs / Henry Cowell -- Organum for orchestra, arranged for piano by John Kirkpatrick / Carl Ruggles -- 22; Protest / Charles Ives.
  - Dvorák, Antonín, 1841-1904 Humoreske, op. 101 no. 7, undated, 1 score (4 leaves); Print Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0931)
  - Elgar, Edward, 1857-1934 Salut d'amour, undated, 1 score (3 leaves); Print (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0932)
  - Gallagher, Paul, 1953-2012 Untitled duo for violin and cello, 1986, 1 score (11 leaves); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For violin and cello Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0933)
  - Gibson, Jon Return, 1988, 1 part (2 pages); Manuscript (ozalid copy) Instrumentation: Keyboard part Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0934)
  - Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003 Trio for violin, cello, and piano, 1989, 2 parts; Print Hermes Beard Press Instrumentation: For violin, cello, and piano Not marked Parts for violin and cello. (Box 40, Folder 0935)
  - Humphrey, Doris, 1895-1958 Dance rhythms, 1935, 1 score (1 leaf); Print (photocopy) Instrumentation: For percussion ensemble Not marked. Notated by Wallingford Riegger. From Percussion IV, 1935. Additional name: Riegger, Wallingford, 1885-1961 (Box 40, Folder 0936)
  - Jack, Adrian, 1943- Beginner's fingers, 1986, 1 score (2 leaves); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0937)
  - Johnston, Ben Sonata for microtonal piano, 1967?, 1 score(9 pages); Manuscript (ozalid copy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0938)
  - Jolas, Betsy Trois études campanaires, 1980, 1 score (5 leaves); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For piano or keyboard carillon Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0939)
  - Kirkpatrick, William Song of the candlefly. Concept 1, undated, 2 typescript leaves; Typescript Instrumentation: For pianist and actor Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0940)
  - Kurtág, György Játékok. Book 5, 1990, 1 score (24 leaves); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Any markings are on the original, not this photocopy. Accompanied by program notes and a list of the movements for use at the Almeida Festival. (Box 40, Folder 0941)
  - Lim, Ban-Hong Remembrance, undated, 1 score (3 leaves); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. Pages numbered 7-9. Title and composer name transcribed from supplied transliteration of Malaysian characters. (Box 40, Folder 0942)
  - Newhouse, Brian Look strange, on this island now, undated, 1 score (22 leaves); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For flute, clarinet, bass clarinet, 3 trombones, percussion, guitar, and soprano Not marked. Title from first line of text which is by W. H. Auden. The envelope housing this score is marked Brian" and "Newhouse" but the attribution on the score looks like B. G. Newham. Additional name: Auden, W. H. (Wystan Hugh), 1907-1973 (Box 40, Folder 0943)
  - Paderewski, Ignace Jan, 1860-1941 Menuet à la antique, undated, 1 score (5 leaves); Print (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0944)
  - Pickard, Kevin Barry Ex nihilo, 1973, 1 score (5 leaves); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For baritone, piano, and offstage instruments Not marked. Text by W. H. Auden. Additional name: Auden, W. H. (Wystan Hugh), 1907-1973 (Box 40, Folder 0945)
  - Pickard, Kevin Barry Fuss ou bien pieds, undated, 1 score (3 leaves); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0946)
    Fuss ou bien pieds -- La pluie sur la rive Styx -- Zurn Beispiel.
  - Polonio, Eduardo, 1941- Fantasia variaciones bajo fianza Rebelais en un trono, 1983, 1 score (3 leaves); Print Instrumentation: For piano and tape Not marked. Two typescript leaves and 1 leaf of music. (Box 40, Folder 0947)
  - Premanarida, Weerachat, 1958- Pap wed, undated, 1 score (8 pages on 4 leaves); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0948)
  - Rosenzweig, Michael Interlude for solo piano, undated, 1 score (8 pages); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0949)
  - Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921 Feés, 1906, 1 score (9 pages); Print Durand Instrumentation: For voice and piano 4-hands Not marked. Text by T. F. Banville. Accompanied by print from scan. Use this copy for service to preserve the original. Additional name: Banville, Théodore Faullain de, 1823-1891 (Box 40, Folder 0950)
  - Scelsi, Giacinto, 1905-1988 Duo for horn and contrabass, undated, 1 score (13 pages); Manuscript (reproduction) Instrumentation: For horn and contrabass Not marked. The score bears no attribution to Scelsi and the work is not currently in his works list. Efforts are being made to ascertain the composer. (Box 40, Folder 0951)
  - Sellars, James, 1943- Piano sonata no. 5, 1985, 1 score (8 leaves); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0952)
  - Sellars, James, 1943- Suite for military band. Waltz, 1981, 1 score (pages 7-15) and 4 parts; Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For speaker/dancer, piano, soprano saxophone, trumpet, contrabass, and percussion Not marked. Parts for Saxophone, trumpet, percussion, and contrabass. First line of text: When we're gliding along on the back of a mare at the fairgrounds. (Box 40, Folder 0953)
  - Senfl, Ludwig, approximately 1426-1542 or 1543 Istum crucis socium et regni credimus, undated, 1 transparency; Transparency Instrumentation: For 4 equal voices Not marked. Received in container with material by Sylvano Bussotti. (Box 40, Folder 0954)
  - Taylor, A. Diablo's march and virgin sacrifice, 1969, 1 score (7 pages); Holograph (ink) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0955)
  - Toovey, Andrew Embrace, 1990, 1 part (4 pages); Reproduction of manuscript Boosey & Hawkes Instrumentation: For two pianos Not marked. Only the Piano 2 part. Written for James Clapperton and Yvar Mikhashoff. (Box 40, Folder 0956)
  - Vigeland, Nils Calliope waltz, 1993, 1 score (6 leaves); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0957)
  - Vrieslander, Otto, 1880-1950 Pierrot lunaire. Selections, 1911, 1 score (12 leaves); Print G. Müller Instrumentation: For voice and piano Not marked. Pages xxv-xxxvi. Texts by Albert Giraud. Edition and translation by Ottor Erich Hartleben. Additional name: Giraud, Albert, 1860-1929 (Box 40, Folder 0958)
    Landschaft -- Die Harfe.
  - Young, Shui-Ting Tide, 1988, 1 score (5 leaves); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano Not marked. (Box 40, Folder 0959)
  - Unknown Schemes, no. 1-2. Selections, undated, 1 score (5 leaves); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For unspecified duets and trios Not marked. Score consists chiefly of prose directions and graphic notation. (Box 40, Folder 0960)
    Duet from Scheme I -- Duet from Scheme II -- Trio from Scheme I -- Trio from Scheme II.
  - Unknown Quartet for clarinet, violin, violoncello and pianoforte, 1982, 1 score (34 leaves); Holograph (photocopy) Instrumentation: For clarinet, violin, violoncello and piano Not marked. "For Richard Pye with affection and gratitude". (Box 40, Folder 0961)
- Composer groupings, 1901-1987, VI.; Folder 962-Folder 1062
  This series contains scores that had been grouped together by Yvar Mikhashoff into folders or envelopes. The series also includes accompanying material such as notes, programs, and clippings.
  Arranged alphabetically by composer surname into 9 subseries:
  A. Sylvano Bussotti
  B. John Cage
  C. George Crumb
  D. Lukas Foss
  E. Percy Grainger
  F. Charles Ives
  G. Mauricio Kagel
  H. Ernst Krenek
  I. Virgil Thomson
  - Sylvano Bussotti, 1980-1986, VI.A; Item 962-973
    Sylvano Bussotti composed his Le Racine, pianobar pour Phèdre in 1980 and wrote the part of Monsieur Fred, the onstage pianist in the opera, for Mikhashoff. Folder 962 below contains the score that was used by Mikhashoff during the world-premiere and later performances. Mikhashoff later made a solo piano transcription of the work, although he did not completely write out every movement that he included in his transcription. It appears that he performed the other movements from the original score, condensing the piano and vocal parts as he played. Mikhashoff also worked with Bussotti on a different version of the opera reduced just for piano and singer.
    Arranged with the original full score first followed by various derivations.
    - Bussotti, Sylvano Racine, pianobar pour Phèdre, 1980, 1 score (54 pages); Holograph (reproduction) Instrumentation: For solo piano Heavily marked for performance with many inserts and sections re-notated by Mikhashoff. The score is bound in red velvet. It is in fragile condition. Two full copies, produced from scans, are also included. They should be used rather than the original. (Box 41, Folder 0962)
    - Bussotti, Sylvano Racine, pianobar pour Phèdre. La romanza al sol, undated, 1 score (3 leaves); Manuscript (photocopy) Instrumentation: For solo piano All markings on the original, not the photocopy Selection on leaves 1-2 matches original score from the green star on page 17 through page 22. Leaf 3 is in Mikhashoff's hand. A match to the original score has not yet been identified. (Box 41, Folder 0963)
    - Bussotti, Sylvano Racine, pianobar pour Phèdre. Coda, 1981, 1 score (8 leaves); Manuscript (ink) Instrumentation: For solo piano There are a few pencil emendations and changes made using white-out fluid. Selection matches original score from page 58 through the end of the piece. (Box 41, Folder 0964)
    - Bussotti, Sylvano Racine, pianobar pour Phèdre. Coda, undated, 1 score (2 pages); Manuscript (pencil) Instrumentation: For solo piano Some additional, possibly unrelated music in ink The beginning of this matches the original score beginning at page 58 and ends at page 62. There is a written message, possibly by Bussotti, at the top of page 1. The music consists of Intro, Strophe 1, Strophe 2 (optional), Strophe 3, and Strophe 4. These divisions do not appear on the original score. (Box 41, Folder 0965)